thelongeststay.com 2016-10-27

# Privacy Policy | The Longest Stay

The Longest Stay has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: [www.thelongeststay.com](http://www.thelongeststay.com/)

The Longest Stay is the trading name of The Longest Stay Ltd. Any information that you provide to us will be stored and processed in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. We will hold and transmit your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties except as described under the heading “your data” below or in our Privacy Policy. If you object to your Information being transferred or used in this way please do not register.

## Your Data

When becoming a new customer you agree to our terms and conditions and privacy policy. The information you provide shall be held and may be used by The Longest Stay, and disclosed to associate companies of The Longest Stay for the following purposes: Order processing; Informing you about forthcoming events organised by or on behalf of The Longest Stay, telling you about products, services and offers available from The Longest Stay, and operating and administering such products, services and offers; processing of applications for, and administering membership of, this website; providing you with updates and information about The Longest Stay; and helping The Longest Stay through analysis and assessment to better understand and develop our business, including new and innovative products and services.

Communication between The Longest Stay and you may be by email, phone, letter or other electronic means. IMPORTANT: By registering with The Longest Stay and/or using our website you consent to The Longest Stay using your data in this way.

When becoming a new customer on line with The Longest Stay or purchasing goods on line we record your Internet IP address for our records for reference to any fraudulent payment transactions.

## Cookies

****We use session based cookies to help you maintain your shopping basket and any details you submit during your visit. We do not store permanent cookies on your computer, and you will need to login with your registered user name and password each time you wish to purchase goods from the website.

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can email [sales@thelongeststay.com](mailto:sales@thelongeststay.com) .
